fathomseo.com 2006-06-29

# Fathom SEO Privacy Policy

Fathom SEO Privacy Policy  

* * *

> To view our Terms of Use - [click here](http://www.fathomseo.com/TermsofUse.asp).

Introduction

This Website Privacy Policy demonstrates the commitment of Fathom SEO, to protecting the privacy of visitors to our Website and sets forth our Website information collection and management practices. By using this Website, you acknowledge and consent to our practices described below.

Information That We Collect

You may use our Website without disclosing to us any personally identifiable information. Fathom SEO collects personally identifiable information from you only if you choose to provide it when you sign up to receive newsletters or contact our firm by e-mail. We use this information only to respond to your comments or questions or to provide services related to the specific purpose for which you submitted the information.

As a firm, we also receive non-personally identifiable information through cookies and log files when you access our Website. Certain technical information, such as your IP address, page views, operating systems, Web browser software, and referring and destination Website, is automatically collected from your computer. Cookies are small computer files that we transfer to your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to statistically monitor how many people are using our site and for what purpose. Fathom SEO, use information gathered from cookies and log files solely to generate broad demographic and user statistics to improve the content of our Website. We do not link any information obtained from cookies or log files to personally identifiable information. You are always free to decline cookies if your browser permits, but in that case, some portions of our Website may not operate properly.

Our Information Disclosure Practices

Our firm does not share your information with any third parties without your consent except as follows: (1) where such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law or protect the safety of our users or others, or (2) with service providers performing services on our behalf, which may include communications, database, event management, hosting, mailing and marketing services. Any service providers employed by our company will have access to your information solely to the extent necessary to enable them to perform the service on our behalf.

Fathom SEO has no obligation to monitor our Website or the use of our Website, or to retain the content of any user session. However, Fathom SEO, reserves the right at all times to monitor, review and/or retain any information to comply with the law or protect the safety of our users or others.

Security

Our Website employs industry standard security measures designed to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of information you provide us via our Website. You should know, however, Fathom SEO cannot fully eliminate such risks, and Fathom SEO is not responsible for unauthorized access to information by hackers or others who have obtained such access through illegal means.

Linked Sites

Fathom SEO, may include links to external sites on its Website from time to time. The inclusion of any link does not imply our endorsement of such external Website or the products and services offered at such site. If you link to a third party site from our Website, any information you reveal on that site is not subject to this Privacy Statement. Therefore, you should consult the privacy policies of each site you visit.

Information from Children

Fathom SEO does not direct its website to children under thirteen years of age. Individuals under 18 should consult with their parent or guardian about the use of this Website.

Changes and Questions

The Internet is evolving rapidly, as are the ways in which people use the Internet and the laws surrounding such use. Fathom SEO, therefore reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new Privacy Policy at this location. Please check this page periodically for changes. You can determine if this Privacy Policy has been revised by referring to the "Last Updated" date at the bottom of this page. Your use of our Website constitutes your acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy as amended or revised by us, as a search engine marketing group, and you should therefore review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are aware of its terms.

Contact Our Firm

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or any questions about our site, you can send an email to our search engine marketing company at [ info@fathomSEO.com](mailto:info@fathomseo.com).

Last Updated: January 8, 2006
